<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DashWorld WorldBuilding</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on DashWorld WorldBuilding</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ranks</title>
      <link>http://example.org/ranks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://example.org/ranks/</guid>
      <description>All Ranks inherent perks from previous ranks Member Perk Description /recipes The ablity to see all custom crafting and item recipes that we have created as a server /graves The ablity to see where you died and to save your items from despawning /rtp The ability to randomly telport around the map every 10 minutes /pvp toggle The ability to toggle your personal pvp on or off Rewards You will get 10 Ⓟ (Player Points) per hour you play on the server (Being AFK on the server does not count towards your playtime) /pointshop A place to spend your Ⓟ (Player Points) /menu An interactive menu for the server Acquaintance Perk Description /heads Acess to head database heads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rules</title>
      <link>http://example.org/rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://example.org/rules/</guid>
      <description>Bigotry and discrimination of any kind is prohibited. This includes hate speech, symbols, jokes, skins and anything else that creates an unsafe environment for people of a particular group.
NSFW text, images, builds, skins, etc will not be permitted.
Be respectful of other players. Respect others boundaries, and do not harass, threaten, impersonate, share personal information without consent, or otherwise intentionally harm others.
Do not grief. This includes both destruction or defacing of builds or nearby areas, as well as unwanted block spam.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donate</title>
      <link>http://example.org/donate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 19:59:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://example.org/donate/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynmap</title>
      <link>http://example.org/dynmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 19:59:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://example.org/dynmap/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>